<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on kubuntuclaps blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on kubuntuclaps blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cracking series #1: CD protected games</title>
      <link>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-1/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Welcome to my first post, im very excited about it so let&amp;rsquo;s start.
I was playing some videogames when i got curious of how games are cracked, then i downloaded an old game from my childhood&amp;hellip; Sonic Adventure DX.
Let&amp;rsquo;s dig into it. I downloaded the disc version from The Seven Seas website that is blocked for a lot of ISPs, after installing it without the DEVIANCE crack, i go into the game folder and find two .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cracking series #2: Steam games</title>
      <link>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-2/</guid>
      <description>Hi! In the previous chapter we tried to crack a CD protected game, which i failed in the attempt so, i really wanted to crack myself this game so i had a good idea&amp;hellip;
I had bought the game on steam, so why not crack the steam version? Don&amp;rsquo;t waste any more time and let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
Files I created a copy outside of steamapps folder (in case of something bad happens) and closed my steam session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cracking series #3: Steam multiplayer crack</title>
      <link>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/10/cracking-series-3/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new episode of my cracking series, today we will see how i cracked 90% (or even more) of the steam library with a simple thing.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started Well, i downloaded Sonic Generations from our seven seas website, and i see the crack is a .DLL file (steam_api.dll) which 1337 people archieve the way of emulate it (and get online functions)&amp;hellip;
How the file works? In a simple way, it emulates steam and spoofs the GameID which is a number to identify the game XD and spoofs it into Spacewar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
